Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - D. Floyd and Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1659; D. Floyd and Ms Kim perform on stage at Freedom Plaza for the D. C. Emancipation Day festivities. In front of the crowd D. Floyd and Ms Kim pace away from each other with their backs turned while holding microphones.
  - Doug E. Fresh performing at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1660; Doug E. Fresh raps into the microphone. Doug E. Fresh performing on stage for the D. C. Emancipation Day festivities.
  - Eric Benet performing at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1661; Eric Benet holds one fist clenched in the air. Fans in the crowd can be seen taking photos. Drum cymbals are visible on stage.
  - Fans at the D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1662; D. C. Emancipation Day participant holds one fist clenched to the sky at Freedom Plaza.
  - Medea Benjamin and Kevin Danaher at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1663; Medea Benjamin and Kevin Danaher smile and dance at a D. C. Emancipation Day concert at Freedom Plaza.
  - Pee Wee dancing on stage at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1664; Pee Wee dances on stage in front of the crowd at Freedom Plaza. Fans in the crowd look on and take pictures. Keyboard instruments are visible on stage.
  - Quisy performing with Still Familiar at D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-04-26; 199chippy_1665; Quisy performs with the microphone on stage with Still Familiar. Still Familiar band members are visible in the background holding timbales.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1675; A young fan sleeps on mom's shoulders. Junk Yard Band performs on stage in the background.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1676; A young fan dances in the center of the crowd at the 2015 Funk Parade.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1677; A young fan dances in the center of the crowd at the 2015 Funk Parade.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1678; Junk Yard Band performs in front of a crowd of fans. Junk Yard Band headlines at the 2015 Funk Parade.
  - Ian MacKaye, Animal, and Josh on Bass at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1679; Ian MacKaye poses with BLACK ALLEY band members Animal and Josh on Bass at the 2015 Funk Parade.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1680; A fan joins Junk Yard Band on stage at the 2015 Funk Parade. Junk Yard Band member House in the background playing the bass.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1681; Bugs, founder of Junk Yard Band, performs on stage with a young fan. Keyboard instruments are visible in the background.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1682; Junk Yard Band members perform on stage at the 2015 Funk Parade. One band member points one finger to the sky. A young fan joins Junk Yard Band on stage.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1683; Members of Junk Yard Band perform on stage at the 2015 Funk Parade. In the background several musical instruments are visible.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fan, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1684; A woman in round sunglasses grooves to Junk Yard Band.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1685; Junk Yard Band performs in front of fans at the 2015 Funk Parade. Several musical instruments are visible including.
  - Junk Yard Band performing at the 2015 Funk Parade, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1686; Junk Yard Band performs in front of fans at the 2015 Funk Parade. On stage Junk Yard Band members play musical instruments including a cow bell, guitars, and drums.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1687; A couple of Junk Yard fans hold their arms to the sky. Junk Yard Band headlines the 2015 Funk Parade.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1688; Black and white photo of a woman with natural white hair with one hand to the sky. Fan grooves to Junk Yard Band.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1689; A child dances in the center of the crowd of fans to Junk Yard Band.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1690; A young fan on the shoulders of an older fan mid clap. A crowd of fans in the background smile. Industrial Bank on U Street can be seen in the background.
  - Ms Kim performing with Familiar Face at Society Restaurant and Lounge, 2015-05-02; 199chippy_1691; Ms Kim holds a microphone in her right hand while performing with Familiar Face.
  - Elijah Balbed, DJ Blakberri, Brad Clements, and Chip Py at a cookout, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1698; From left to right Elijah Balbed, DJ Blakberri, Brad Clements, and Chip Py sit together on a deck during a cookout before a show. Two dogs also join the gathering.
  - Darryl Levine arriving at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1699; Darryl Levine removes his glasses as he arrives at Howard Theatre before a show in honor of the third anniversary of Chuck Brown's passing.
  - Elijah Balbed warming up at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1700; Elijah Balbed warms up on the tenor saxophone backstage before a show in honor of the third anniversary of Chuck Brown's passing at Howard Theatre.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go warming up at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1701; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go warms up on guitar before a show in honor of the third anniversary of Chuck Brown's passing. A drum set is visible in the foreground.
  - Big G and Peekaso at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1702; From left to right Big G and Peekaso backstage at Howard Theatre after the third anniversary show of Chuck Brown's passing.
  - Big G, Peekaso, and Weensey backstage with a crowd at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1703; Big G snap a photo of Weensey folding a painting completed by Peekaso during a show in honor of the third anniversary of Chuck Brown's passing. Peekaso (to the right) looks on.
  - KK with a fan at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1704; KK poses with a fan at Howard Theatre after the third anniversary show of Chuck Brown's passing.
  - KK arriving at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1705; KK walks towards Howard Theatre for the third anniversary show of Chuck Brown's passing. Behind her vehicle are visible.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go at Howard Theatre, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1706; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go sits quietly before the a show in honor of the third anniversary of Chuck Brown's passing at Howard Theatre. To his right is a trombone. Chip Py, the photographer of this image, is reflected in the mirror.
  - Whiteboy on the cover of City Paper, 2015-05-17; 199chippy_1707; Cover of City Paper featuring Whiteboy and an article about Rare Essence.
  - Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar at Society Lounge, 2015-05-24; 199chippy_1666; Ms Kim holds a covered wine glass. Ms Kim quick chats with a fan. Ms Kim holds a speaker stand.
  - Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar at Society Lounge, 2015-05-24; 199chippy_1667; Ms Kim sings into the microphone while performing on stage with Still Familiar.
  - Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar at Society Lounge, 2015-05-24; 199chippy_1668; Ms Kim performs with Still Familiar at Society Restaurant and Lounge. Ms Kim and Still Familiar band members point fingers to the crowd.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performing with Still Familiar on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore, 2015-05-24; 199chippy_1669; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs with Still Familiar at Music Center at Strathmore. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go sings into the microphone. Still Familiar band member plays the keyboard in the background.
  - O and D. Floyd performing with Still Familiar at Society Restaurant and Lounge, 2015-05-24; 199chippy_1692; From left to right O plays trumpet and D. Floyd plays tenor saxophone while performing with Still Familiar.
  - Member of Da Party Crasherz at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1639; Party Crasherz entertainer poses at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle. Party Crasherz wearing eyeglasses. A woman stands behind Party Crasherz.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and Mr. Marcus Young embrace at 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1640; From left to right Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go greets Mr. Marcus Young at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle. People standing in the background are visible.
  - Big Tony and his stage manager arrive at 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1641; Big Tony of Trouble Funk (left) and his stagehand arrive at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle. Big Tony is wearing a black hat and black t-shirt.
  - KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1642; KK on stage at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle. KK looks to the left. Mr. Marcus Young is in the background.
  - Fans on the front row at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1643; Fans in the front row dance to the music at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performing with Chuck Brown Band, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1644; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performing. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go holds the microphone in his right hand. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go holding guitar.
  - Fans backstage at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1645; A fan backstage fans themselves with a WPGC fan while smiling.
  - Children backstage at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1646; Band members babies relax backstage on stage equipment during the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle.
  - 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle set list, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1647; Chuck Brown band's set list for the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle.
  - Ice performing with Chuck Brown Band, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1648; Ice plays the guitar with Chuck Brown band at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle in 2015. A fellow band member plays the drums in the background.
  - Ice and his daughter performing with Chuck Brown Band, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1649; Ice and his daughter on stage with Chuck Brown Band. Ice plays the electric guitar. Ice's daughter looks directly into the camera.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1650; Sweet Cherie sings into the mic with one arm in the air while bubbles surround her. Keyboard instruments and microphones are visible on stage.
  - Sweet Cherie and Leon Rawlings performing with Chuck Brown Band, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1651; Sweet Cherie and Leon Rawlings perform on stage. Sweet Cherie sings into the microphone with both eyes closed. Rawlings blows into the trombone.
  - Fans at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1652; Fans stand and watch the band at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle in 2015. One fan stands with both arms in the air.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle in 2015, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1653; Chuck Brown Band members hold one finger to the sky. Fans look on and hold one finger/ hand in the air.
  - KK with Elwood Yango Sawyer, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1654; KK smiles with her peace fingers. KK poses with Elwood Yango Sawyer and other fans.
  - Jazz Web and Trouble Funk stagehands at 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1655; From left to right Trouble Funk stagehand and Jaz Web stagehand for the 2015 National Capital Barbecue Battle. Jaz Web smiling.
  - BLACK ALLEY at the D. C. Emancipation Day at Freedom Plaza, 2015-06-28; 199chippy_1656; Members of BLACK ALLEY and friends pose with peace fingers.
  - Child taps a drum during the Still Familiar performance on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore, 2015-07-15; 199chippy_1670; Still Familiar band member Jammin Jeff invites a young fan on stage to play the drums. A young fan joins Still Familiar on stage to play the drums. Quisy performs with the microphone. Several musical instruments are visible on stage including congas, a guitar, and a saxophone.
  - Claire Lieberman dances to Still Familiar at Music Center at Strathmore, 2015-07-15; 199chippy_1671; Claire Lieberman and other fans dance on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore. Still Familiar performs on stage.
  - Ms Kim performing with Still Familiar on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore, 2015-07-15; 199chippy_1672; Ms Kim takes a selfie with a microphone in her hand and the crowd of fans in the background. Still Familiar perform on stage. Fans dance at the edge of the stage.
  - Still Familiar performing on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore, 2015-07-15; 199chippy_1673; Bokeh' photo of Still Familiar and the crowd of fans on the lawn at Music Center at Strathmore. Still Familiar perform in front of a crowd of fans. Guitars, drums, and microphones are visible on stage.
  - 2015 Funk Parade fans, 2015-07-15; 199chippy_1674; A young funk fan smiles for the camera at the 2015 Funk Parade. She points to a platform shoe with a fish inside.
  - Quisy performing with Still Familiar at Society Restaurant and Lounge, 2015-10-25; 199chippy_1693; Close-up of Quisy performing with Still Familiar at Society Lounge. Quisy sings into the microphone.
  - Still Familiar at Society performing at Society Restaurant and Lounge, 2015-10-25; 199chippy_1694; Still Familiar on stage together at Society Restaurant and Lounge. From left to right are Jammin Jeff on drums, O on trumpet, Beastin Geason on bass guitar, D. Floyd on alto saxophone, and Ulysses Holmes keyboard player.
  - Elijah Balbed performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1734; Elijah Balbed plays tenor saxophone while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Brad Clements on trumpet and Greg Boyer on trombone are visible in the background.
  - Sweet Cherie and Kevin Jones at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1735; Sweet Cherie leans over and sings to Kevin Jones in the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at Bethesda Blues and Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1736; From left to right Brad Clements on trumpet, Greg Boyer on trombone, and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go on guitar and vocals perform with Chuck Brown Band. Brad Clements and Greg Boyer dance while Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go smiles.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at Bethesda Blues and Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1737; From left to right Elijah Balbed plays tenor saxophone, Brad Clements plays trumpet, Greg Boyer plays trombone, and KK sings and dances while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go and KK performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1738; From left to right Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go plays an electric guitar and KK sings and reaches towards the audience while performing with Chuck Brown Band.
  - Sweet Cherie performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1739; Sweet Cherie smiles and plays the keys while performing with Chuck Brown Band. Mighty Moe is visible in the background playing congas.
  - Mighty Moe and Sweet Cherie perform with Chuck Brown Band, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1740; Sweet Cherie smiles while playing the keyboard. Mighty Moe plays the congas. They are performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1741; KK and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go sing together on stage during a performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club. Elijah Balbed and Brad Clements can be seen playing the tenor saxophone and trumpet (respectively). Mr. Marcus Young can be seen playing the keyboard, and Doug Crowley is on the electric guitar. Fan are cheering below the stage.
  - Doug Crowley, KK, Sweet Cherie, Greg Boyer, and Brad Clements performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1742; Sweet Cherie and KK lead Chuck Brown Band at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club. Greg Boyer and Brad Clements can be seen dancing with their trombone and trumpet. Doug Crowley plays an electric guitar in the rear.
  - Chuck Brown Band performing at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1743; Chuck Brown Band performing at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club. Sweet Cherie plays the keyboard as Greg Boyer and KK cheer her on. Mighty Moe can be seen playing the congas in the background.
  - Kwick Foot and Mighty Moe performing with Chuck Brown Band at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1744; Mighty Moe plays the congas while Kwick Foot plays the drums during their performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club.
  - KK dances with a fan at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1745; KK and a fan smile as they hold hands and dance. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go is singing in the background. Chuck Brown Band is performing at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club.
  - Elijah Balbed, Bad Clements, and Greg Boyer at Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1746; Elijah Balbed with an alto saxophone (right), Brad Clements with a trumpet (center), and Greg Boyer with a trombone (left) all smile and pose for a photograph before their performance with Chuck Brown Band at the Bethesda Blues and Jazz Supper Club.
  - DJ Blakberri with her child at WPGC Studios, 2016-01-30; 199chippy_1747; DJ Blakberri holds her child up to the microphone as the baby reaches out for it. Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go can be seen smiling at the baby.
  - Person dancing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1853; A person smiles while dancing at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Unknown Musicians performing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1854; Unknown trombone player performs on stage at La Fontaine Bleue. A unknown trumpet players is on stage as well.
  - Unknown musician performing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1855; Unknown singer performs on stage at La Fontaine Bleue. A another person can be seen playing the tambourine.
  - People dancing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1856; Fans can be seen dancing during a concert at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Unknown musician performing at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1857; Unknown singer performs on stage at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Shawn Cosby performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1858; Professional dancer Shawn Cosby (right) performs on stage with Maiesha (not pictured). An unknown dancer can also be seen (left).
  - Maiesha and Shawn Cosby performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1859; Maiesha sings on stage at La Fontaine Bleue. Professional dancer Shawn Cosby (far right) dances on stage for the performance. An unknown dancer can be seen in the center.
  - Fans dance at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1860; Fans dance during a concert at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Fans dance at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1861; Fans dance during a concert at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Fans dance at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1862; Three fans dance at the front of the stage during a concert at La Fontaine Bleue. Other fans are visible.
  - Buggs performing with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-13; 199chippy_1863; Buggs holds the microphone out towards a fan during a performance with Maiesha and the Hip Huggers at La Fontaine Bleue. Fans can be seen dancing.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1842; Keith Angelo dances on stage during a performance at Takoma Station Tavern. Other performers can be seen in the background.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1843; Keith Angelo dances on stage during a performance at Takoma Station Tavern. Other performers can be seen in the background.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1844; Keith Angelo dances on stage during a performance at Takoma Station Tavern. Other performers can be seen in the background.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1845; Keith Angelo dances on stage during a performance at Takoma Station Tavern. Other performers can be seen in the background.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1846; Keith Angelo leans towards the audience during a performance at Takoma Station Tavern. Two backing vocalists can be seen on stage. Fans can be seen watching from below, some are recording the performance. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1847; Keith Angelo performs on stage at Takoma Station Tavern. Two backing vocalists can be seen on stage. Fans can be seen watching from below, some are recording the performance. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1848; Keith Angelo performs on stage at Takoma Station Tavern. Two backing vocalists can be seen on stage. Fans can be seen in the image. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Keith Angelo performs at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1849; Keith Angelo performs on stage at Takoma Station Tavern. The image was shot from the audience's perspective, and fans are visible from of the stage. One fans looks behind to face the camera. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Keith Angelo poses for a photograph on stage at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1850; Keith Angelo turns away from the audience to pose for a photograph. Other musicians and fans crowd the stage to get in frame for the photograph. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Keith Angelo poses for a photograph on stage at Takoma Station Tavern, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1851; Keith Angelo turns away from the audience to pose for a photograph. Other musicians and fans crowd the stage to get in frame for the photograph. This event is likely an album release celebration.
  - Martin 'Made in the City' Cooper and Too Smooth at La Fontaine Bleue, 2016-03-27; 199chippy_1852; Party promoter Martin 'Made in the City' Cooper and Too Smooth pause for photograph at La Fontaine Bleue.
  - Darryl Levine backstage at 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert, Freedom Plaza, 2016-04-17; 199chippy_1789; Darryl Levine leaving against a blockade backstage at 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert, Freedom Plaza.
  - Big Tony performs with Trouble Funk for 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert at Freedom Plaza, 2016-04-17; 199chippy_1790; Big Tony plays bass while performing with Trouble Funk for 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert at Freedom Plaza.
  - Fans at 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert at Freedom Plaza, 2016-04-17; 199chippy_1791; Fans smile and dance at the 2016 D. C. Emancipation Day Celebration Concert at Freedom Plaza.